你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
普丽娅一会要跟我用Skype视频
Oh, uh, Priya's calling in a few minutes on Skype,
我们准备共进晚餐
and we are gonna have a dinner date.
现在是孟买时间早上八点
It's 8 o'clock in the morning in Mumbai.
她怎么就吃起晚饭来了
How can she have dinner?
好吧  随你怎么说
Fine, whatever.
那普丽娅就吃早餐好了
Priya will be having breakfast.
好吧  所以严格来讲你们俩不是共进晚餐
All right, so technically it's not a dinner date.
也许你勉强可以把这称为共进早晚餐
I suppose you could call it a, uh, dinfast date.
不过你要是真这么叫的话
But if you did, you'd open yourself
你肯定会被别人笑死  人家肯定会说
to peer-based mocking, such as,
莱纳德  你昨晚跟普丽娅的早晚餐吃的好吗
"Hey, Leonard, how was your dinfast with Priya last night?"
听起来不像是在笑话我呀
That doesn't sound like mocking.
我还没说完呢
You didn't let me finish.
早晚餐
Dinfast.
那是大豆蜡的蜡烛吗
Are those soy-based candles?
不知道  怎么了
I don't know. Why?
石蜡蜡烛可能含有致癌物
Paraffin candles may contain carcinogens.
当然啦  你要是想吃顿早晚餐
Unless lung cancer is the ambiance
还搭上肺癌的话  我也不拦你
you were going for at your dinfast.
早晚餐
Dinfast.
我不想无礼
Listen, I don't want to be rude,
可是普丽娅随时都会打来
but Priya's gonna be calling any minute, so...
对哦  普丽娅
Oh, yes, Priya.
莱纳德  你知道我从来
Leonard, you know I make a point of
都不干涉你的私事
never interfering in your personal affairs.
没错  我也一直很欣赏你这点
Yes, I've always admired that about you.
那是当然
As well you should.
但是我这次要破例了
But I'm going to make an exception here.
又来了
Oh, good.
普丽娅回印度去发展自己的法律事业
Priya has moved back to India to pursue her law career.
你与其花这些时间绝望地挣扎
Instead of desperately trying
费劲心思地保持这段跨洲恋情
to keep this intercontinental relationship alive,
你还不如找点别的兴趣爱好呢
you could use that time to take up a hobby.
兴趣爱好
A hobby?
没错
Yes.
我最近得知堪萨斯州一个家伙
I read recently about a fellow in Kansas
拿麻绳团了一个巨大的球
with an enormous ball of twine.
我认为你可以跟他一比高下
I bet you could give him a run for his money.
你知道吗  有些人可能会说
You know, some people might say that it's great
我们俩保持这种异地恋是精神可嘉的事
that we're trying to make things work long distance.
他们会说
They'd say things like,
爱情不会被你们俩之间的距离所打败
"Love is stronger than the miles between you".
等有一天我掌权了  我肯定会灭掉这帮人
When I rise to power, those people will be sterilized.
你也整天跟艾米视频呀
You video-chat with Amy all the time.
咱俩干的事有什么不同
How is this different?
你不喜欢艾米吗
Don't you like Amy?
我当然喜欢艾米啦
Of course I like Amy.
可我不喜欢普丽娅呀
Well, there's the difference.
不好意思  普丽娅打来了
Excuse me, that's Priya.
莱纳德
Hi, Leonard.
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
我好想你
I miss you.
我也好想你
Oh, I miss you, too.
我怀念以前爱情伴侣们
I miss the old days when your romantic partners
能退回录像店的日子
could be returned to the video store.
谢谢你让我待在这
Thanks for letting me stay here
这样我就不用看着莱纳德跟他女朋友视频了
while Leonard Skypes with his girlfriend.
小意思
Oh, it's no problem.
这种感觉还挺不错的呢
It's actually kind of nice.
你在看书  我也在看书
You reading, me reading.
咱俩就像一对老夫老妻似的
We're like an old married couple.
咱俩要真是老夫老妻的话
If we were an old married couple,
妻子这个时候就会端上冻柠茶和曲奇饼了
the wife would serve iced tea and snickerdoodles.
我家没有冻柠茶和曲奇饼
I don't have iced tea and snickerdoodles.
尽职的妻子就会去商店买
A good wife would go to the store.
我要离婚
I want a divorce.
很好  你去找律师的路上
Good. On the way to see the lawyer,
别忘了买点冻柠茶和曲奇饼
pick up some tea and cookies.
我还真得说  我挺喜欢你这张新椅子的
I must say, I am enjoying your new chair.
舒服吧
It's great, isn't it?
没错
It is.
符合腰椎曲线
Aligns the lumbar,
支撑住了尾骨  还平衡了臀部
cradles the coccyx, balances the buttocks.
这椅子还真对得起它的名字
This is a chair worthy of the name.
什么名字
What name?
椅子呀
Chair.
好吧  你喜欢就好
Oh, all right, well, I'm glad you like it.
我还是想不通
I mean, I still can't get over the fact
怎么有人就忍心把它给扔了呢
someone just threw it away.
你说什么
What?
就是说呀  这椅子就被丢在路上
Yeah, it was just sitting on the street.
我给了个流浪汉十块钱  让他帮我把这张椅子搬上来的
I paid a homeless guy ten bucks to help me get it up here.
哦天呐  哦天呐
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
你怎么啦
What is wrong?
我刚坐在垃圾上了
I've been sitting in garbage!
谢尔顿  淡定嘛
Sheldon, take it easy.
你去淡定吧  我得去趟浴室
You take it easy! I need to use your shower.
我当年结婚的时候还是太过乐观了
I went into this marriage with so much hope.
浴室地板上有张湿创口贴
There's a wet Band-Aid on the shower floor!
真有意思
This is fun.
我还从来没用过热成型液压机呢
I've never used a hydraulic thermoforming press before.
很赞吧
Pretty sweet, huh?
这个小玩意儿花了学校十七万五千刀
This little baby set the university back 175 grand.
三分钟到了
That's three minutes.
-让我们看看成果如何  -马上好
- Shall we see what we got?  -Hang on
哦也
Oh, yeah.
这真是个有型的三明治
This is one good-looking panini.
把金枪鱼三明治给我
Hand me the tuna melt.
-给  -多谢
- Yep.  - Thank you.
你那跨国异地恋怎么样啦
How's it going with the long-distance love affair?
不容易啊  但我俩正在努力
Not easy, but we're making it work.
你这句"正在努力"包不包括玩些线上耍流氓啊
When you say "Making it work," does that include doing the cyber nasty?
什么
What?
你懂的  就是虚拟的很黄很暴力的那种啊
You know, the virtual pickle tickle.
数字化的嘿嘿咻咻
The digital... bow-chicka-bow-bow.
拜托  伙计  你在说我妹啊
Come on, dude. This is my sister you're talking about.
喂  对你来说
Hey, Leonard jiggling his junk at her
莱纳德在摄像头里对着她抖那货
through a webcam has got to be easier for you to deal with
总要好过他当着她的面拿那货戳她吧
than him actually touching her with it.
我没那么猥琐
There's no junk jiggling.
我们就是聊天而已
We just talk.
你疯了吧
Are you sane?
有了高速互联网  你的指尖下
With high-speed Internet, you have at your fingertips
就是继小手帕之后性爱领域的
the greatest advancement in the field of sex
最伟大的进步啊
since the invention of the washcloth.
我不能那么做
I can't do that.
好吧  你要是不这么做
Well, if you don't,
你就是把普丽娅拱手让给某个
you're gonna lose Priya to some fancy guy in a turban
从小看《印度爱经》插图版长大的头巾男了
who grew up with Kama Sutra coloring books.
你怎么能这么种族歧视呢
How can you be so racist?
拜托  我哪句说错了
Oh, come on, tell me I'm wrong.
莱纳德  很好
Oh, Leonard, good.
找到你了
There you are.
我需要你来检查我头上有没有虱子
I need you to check my head for chair lice.
我昨晚查过了  我不能再犯傻了
I did it last night, I'm not doing it again.
没检查别的地儿  对吧
Just his head, right?
我不想聊这事儿
I don't want to talk about it.
佩妮椅子上的虫子没跑到你身上
You didn't catch bugs from Penny's chair.
不对  有虫子
Yes, I did.
现在它们在我的发根毛囊里欢呼雀跃
And now they're cavorting at the base of my hair follicles
就像在红木国家森林公园里跳舞
like dancing hippies at the Redwood National Forest.
谢尔顿  你老是这样
Sheldon, you do this all the time.
你总是纠结于某个傻乎乎的想法
You fixate on some crazy idea
然后无限制地放大
and then blow it way out of proportion.
请举一个例子
Name one time I've ever done that.
比如上次你把GPS追踪器放进垃圾桶里
How about when you put GPS trackers in your garbage
就因为你坚信朝鲜间谍
because you were convinced North Korean spies
在偷你的草稿纸
were stealing your doodles?
还有你坚信是人肉做的鸡块
The chicken nuggets you were sure were human nuggets.
还有那朵奇形怪状的在城里老跟踪你的云
The strangely-shaped cloud that was following you around town.
还有那次你错穿了我的T恤
The time you put on my shirt by mistake
还以为自己又开始长个儿了
and were convinced you'd started growing again.
我说的是  "举一个例子"
I said, "Name one."
你的听力真得练练了
You really need to work on your listening skills.
佩妮
Penny.
佩妮  佩妮
Penny. Penny.
乃好[你好]
Yello.
你得把那个椅子从楼里搬出去
You need to remove that chair from the building.
它是个卫生隐患
It's a health hazard.
好吧  淡定吧  我把家具套给拆下来
Okay, relax. I took off the slipcovers,
送去干洗了  坐垫也熏蒸消毒了
had them dry-cleaned and then fumigated the cushions.
真的吗
Really?
必须的  它现在比我的沙发还干净
Yeah. It's cleaner than my couch.
我还在里面找到了半个鸡蛋灌饼呢
Found half a Hot Pocket in there.
看起来还不错
It certainly looks okay.
有一股强烈的有毒化学药剂味
Has a strong toxic chemical smell.
真让人安心啊
That's reassuring.
坐上去试试呗  谢尔顿
Why don't you give it a try, Sheldon?
好吧
All right.
这椅子挺舒服
It is a comfortable chair.
你为啥不承认你之前反应过激了呢
Why don't you just admit you overreacted?
不必了  多谢
No, thank you.
简直像跟个吉娃娃一起住一样
It's like living with a Chihuahua.
佩妮  佩妮  佩妮
Penny. Penny. Penny.
有事吗  小毛孩
What's up, buttercup?
你必须把那椅子扔了
You have to get rid of the chair.
不
Nope.
佩妮  佩妮  佩妮
Penny. Penny. Penny.
想叽歪啥呀  小蜂鸟
What's the word, hummingbird?
为你安全考量  请到我们那等着
For your safety, please wait in my apartment
让我报警请他们搬走这死亡之椅
as I call the authorities so they may remove the chair of death.
不要
No.
佩妮  佩妮  佩妮
Penny! Penny! Penny!
有何指示  小物理学家
What's the gist, physicist?
作为本街道疾控中心
Under my authority as a self-appointed member
自封的一员  我宣布
of the Centers for Disease Control street team...
此房屋应报废
...these premises are condemned.
作为有着敏锐时尚感的达人
As a man with a keen sense of style,
我必须说  那椅子跟你家一点都不配
I must tell you, that chair does not work with the room.
佩妮
Penny!
Penny.
好了
So, here we are.
我们一起回房上床了
Back in bed together.
是的  一起上床了
Yep, here we are.
好了  那我来直入主题吧
Okay, so I-I guess I'll just jump right in.
好的
All right.
呃  你是个淘气的坏女孩
Uh, you're a naughty girl.
我  我  要  要用爱来鞭挞你
And-And, uh, I-I want to punish you with my love?
搞毛啊
What?
不好吗
Not good?
太可怕了  再来
That's terrible. Try again.
好的
Okay.
你...你一点都不淘气
Uh, uh, you're... not naughty.
你  你是下流
Uh, you're-you're-you're dirty.
你是...
You're...
你是下流的坏女孩
You're a-a dirty girl?
对
Oh, yes.
对  下流之极
Yes, I am.
好好  我摸懂门道了
Yeah, yeah. Uh, okay.
你  你是个...
You're a, you're a...
你是一个  一个下流
You're a-a dirty...
淫秽
disgusting...
叛逆的女孩
revolting girl.
天啊  莱纳德  求你闭嘴吧
God, Leonard, stop talking.
不然等我五分钟先
Why don't you just give me five minutes?
我谷歌一下流程  马上打回给你
I'll Google how to do this. I'll call you right back.
嘘嘘嘘  你闭嘴听我命令行事
Shh-shh-shh. Just be quiet and do what I tell you.
好吧  一如既往  真好
Okay, like usual. Good.
脱掉上衣
Take off your shirt.
好的  脱掉我的小上衣
All rightie. Shirt coming off.
哇啦  男士小咪咪哦
Ta-da! Man nipples.
-我说了闭嘴  -是  长官
- I said be quiet.- Yes, ma'am.
现在脱掉你的短裤
Now take off your shorts.
小裤衩  脱掉
Taking shorts off.
好了
There we go.
赤裸裸  光溜溜  滑嫩嫩
Naked, naked, naked!
好极了
Wonderful.
现在轮到我脱了
Now I'll take off my clothes.
酷
Cool.
你看  宝贝
Here I am, baby.
你想它们了吗
You miss these?
靠  见鬼
Oh, damn it!
哦  莱纳德  这就缴械了?!
Oh, Leonard! Already?!
不  不  不是这样的
No, no! No-no-no!
我屏幕不动了
The screen froze.
可能还在缓冲
It's probably just buffering
你稍等等嘛
Just give it a second.
好吧
Fine.
你父母还好吗
So, how are your mom and dad?
我现在真的不想谈论我父母
Yeah, I really don't want to talk about my parents now.
好的  当然当然
Yeah. Sure, sure.
如果你的视频卡住了
If your video's frozen,
试着重新设置下TCP/IP堆栈
try resetting the TCP/IP stack.
我怎么没想到  谢了
I didn't even think of that. Thanks.
不客气  但请一定通知一声
You're welcome. Please let me know when
等你和你的女友
you and your girlfriend are done
不再占着带宽撸管
hogging the bandwidth for your self-abuse.
我打算要在Netflix上看部电影呢
I'm trying to stream a movie on Netflix in here.
五  六  七  八
Five, six, seven, eight.
*高挑  黝黑  年轻  可爱*
*Tall and tan and young and lovely *
*来自依帕内玛的女孩翩翩而来*
*The girl from Ipanema goes walking*
*当她走过时  每个遇见的人都...*
*And when she passes, each one she passes goes... *
艾米  艾米  艾米
Amy? Amy? Amy?
*哦...*
*Oh... *
你应该注意到你习惯的敲门行为
You are aware that your ritualistic knocking behavior is
是一种强迫症紊乱的表象
symptomatic of obsessive-compulsive disorder.
这不是
Is not.
不是  不是
Is not, is not.
抵赖抵赖你就抵赖吧  请进
Denial. Denial, denial. Come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
你想听我用竖琴弹奏波萨诺伐舞曲吗
Would you like to hear me play a bossa nova standard on the harp?
不想
No.
要不然我换首
How about the theme song
经典电视剧《Diff'rent冲程》的主题曲吧
to the classic television show Diff'rent Strokes?
* 如今的世界已经不再跟着节奏走... *
* Now the world don't move to the beat...*
不想
No.
好吧  我就会这么几首了  什么事
Well, that's every song I know. What's up?
你和佩妮是好朋友对吧
You're good friends with Penny, right?
好朋友  闺蜜
Best friends, besties,
永远的好友  亲如同胞姐妹
BFFs, peas in a pod,
亲得可以穿一条裤子
sisters who would share traveling pants.
你继续
Go on.
我是希望她可以听听你的意见
I was hoping she might listen to you
知道把不干净家具带回家的危险
about the dangers of owning unhygienic furniture.
你这是作为一般教育用途
For general educational purposes,
还是她顺了个浸在霍乱病毒中的酒吧凳回来
or has she acquired a bar stool dipped in cholera?
霍乱是饮水传染的
Cholera is water-borne.
-你这是在嘲笑我  -没错
- You're mocking me. - Yes, I am.
佩妮从大街上拿回了个椅子
Penny has dragged a chair in off the street
这种出处不详的椅子  会危害我们楼里
whose unknown provenance jeopardizes the health and welfare
每位住户的健康和幸福的
of every resident in our building.
谢尔顿  不能就因为你
Sheldon, just because you have a focus on
有神经病一样的洁癖
cleanliness bordering on the psychotic
我也得被你拉下水吧
doesn't mean I have to participate.
好吧  你出个价
All right, name your price.
亲我从未被人亲过的地方
Kiss me where I've never been kissed before.
你是说类似盐湖城的地方吗
You mean like Salt Lake City?
算了  我会跟佩妮说的
Never mind. I'll talk to Penny.
谢谢
Thank you.
那现在听我演奏竖琴好吗
Will you listen to me play my harp now?
不要  我不喜欢竖琴的声音
No. I dislike the sound of the harp.
竖琴在经典电视情景喜剧中的过度使用
Its overuse in classic television sitcoms
每每让我觉得
always makes me think I'm going to
我过去的噩梦又再度上演了
experience an episode from my past.
对不起  妈咪  别生我的气
I'm sorry, Mommy. Don't be mad at me.
别弹了
Don't do that!
我不懂的  霍华德
I don't know about this, Howard.
什么  你对远程做爱有障碍吗
What? You're having trouble with the long-distance lovemaking.
这就是你的法宝
This is your answer.
上面有两个端口能刺激嘴部
There are two interfaces that simulate a human mouth.
你这配一个  在印度的普莉娅配一个
You have one, Priya has one in India.
你只要移动你的嘴唇和舌头
When you move your lips and tongue on yours,
就能传输信号  感觉像是你真的在吻她
it transmits exactly what you're doing to hers.
看见没  网络亲吻
See? Internet kissing.
来试试
Give it a try.
还是算了
I don't think so.
我来试试
I'll try it.
像这样吗
Like this?
差不多  把你的舌头伸进去
Almost. Really get your tongue in there.
激活感应器
to activate the motion sensor.
像这样吗
Like this?
差不多了  要法式舌吻
Close. Really French it.
好点了吗
Better?
对  就这样  太正点了
Yeah, you got it, you got it.
我震精了  这感觉太逼真了
I'm impressed. This is very lifelike.
擦  你居然咬我舌头
Whoa! You just bit my tongue!
轻咬而已  我只想多点情趣
I-I nibbled. I was being playful.
你干嘛要把一切都搞得这么猥琐
Why do you have to make everything weird?
抱歉
Sorry.
好点了吗
Better?
正点
Oh, yeah.
很不错哈
Pretty cool, huh?
商店里买的话没准要两百块
Probably would cost, like, 200 bucks in a store.
是很划算
I do appreciate a bargain.
我去世的奶奶以前有一套这种家具
This entire ensemble once belonged to my dead grandmother.
不是吧
You're kidding.
除了内衣内裤什么都分享了
Everything except bra and panties.
这可是我和维多利亚之间的独家小秘密哟
And they're a leopard-spotted secret I share with Victoria.
而现在是和我了
And now me.
对这沙发椅我只有一个问题
I just have one question about the chair.
什么
And what's that?
你就不担心这个不卫生吗
Aren't you worried about it being unhygienic?
不  完全没有...
No, it's completely fine...
我懂了
Hmm. I get it.
是谢尔顿
Sheldon sent you.
是他让你来找我
He put you up to this.
-不  他没有  -真的吗
- No, he didn't. - Really?
是的  他有  就是他
Yes, he did. He absolutely did.
天啊  艾米  你太不够朋友了
My God, Amy, that's really crappy of you.
真的吗
It is?
当然  你让谢尔顿利用你来操控我
Yeah! Letting Sheldon use you to manipulate me?
我还以为我们是朋友
I thought you were my friend.
不  我们是朋友  请别生我气
No, I am your friend. Please don't be mad at me.
我简直难以置信
I can't even believe this.
你最好还是走吧
You know, maybe you should just go.
不  对不起  真的很对不起
No! No, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我把刚才的话都收回
I take it all back!
看  我坐在你的沙发椅上
Look! I'm, uh, I'm sitting in your chair.
完全没问题
There's nothing wrong with it.
这椅子棒极了
It's a great chair.
求你别把我踢出你的生活
Please let me continue to be part of your world.
怎么了
What's wrong?
椅子里有什么东西在咬我的臀部
Something in the chair's biting my tushy.
但这无所谓
It's not important. Ow!
快站起来
Wait. Get up, get up!
发誓你不会把这事告诉谢尔顿
Swear you won't tell Sheldon what happened!
我发誓
I swear!
我能告诉我医生吗  我觉得我得去打针
Can I tell my doctor? I'm probably gonna need shots!
当然可以
Yeah, sure!
宝贝儿  我觉得我已经懂了
Oh, hey, babe, I think I figured this thing out.
莱纳德  先听我说
Oh, Leonard, listen...
不  你给我听好
No, you listen!
你是我的妞
You're my woman,
我要给你前所未有的快感
and I'm gonna make you feel things you have never felt before.
莱纳德
Leonard...
就是这样  用力叫出我的名字
That's right, say my name...
求我  求我再快点
and beg me for more, 'cause...
我会努力让你达到巅峰
I'm gonna give it to you.
我父母在旁边
My parents are here.
你好  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard...
我也能咬牙切齿用力喊你的名字吗
if I may also say your name.
看呀  从天而降的沙发椅
Check it out. Free chair.
可不是
Yeah.
要是谢尔顿和莱纳德的公寓里有个沙发椅
Hey, you know, if this was in Sheldon and Leonard's apartment,
我就不用老是坐在地板上了
I wouldn't wind up sitting on the floor all the time.
来吗
On three?
-一二三  -抬
- Three! - Three!
哪个二货舍得扔掉这么好的沙发椅哟
What kind of idiot throws away